http://www.swin.edu.au/disclaimer/privacy

Privacy statement
Privacy statement
If you have any questions, issues or concerns (or wish to lodge a complaint in respect of a Privacy matter) please contact Kornel Koffsovitz, Privacy Officer – Associate Director (Legal and Regulatory), Governance and Assurance, on +61 3 9214 5515.
We value your privacy
Swinburne University of Technology acknowledges and respects the privacy of individuals. We advise that much of the information that you may have provided to, or may be asked to provide, to Swinburne University of Technology is 'personal information'. As a general rule, personal information is not released by Swinburne University of Technology to other organisations, except in response to legal requirements such as a subpoena, and information regarding an individual will not be disclosed to a third party without the individual's consent, except where the third party is directly acting as our agent.
Why do we collect your information
This information is normally collected for the purposes of processing your application, registration or inquiry for a Swinburne University of Technology course, activity or interest group. Information that we collect will be used for keeping you informed of upcoming events, improving the student experience and assisting us in improving and marketing our services to you. For more information refer to the Privacy Collection Notice below.
Privacy Collection Notice
Security
Swinburne University uses and implements industry standards for the security and protection of information collected, and this information is securely stored and access is restricted to authorised personnel only, ensuring that your personal information is protected and safeguarded.
Access to your information
You have a right of access to, and alteration of personal information concerning yourself held by the University, in accordance with Government Legislation.
Contact
If staff have any queries in relation to privacy at Swinburne University of Technology, please contact Governance and Assurance.
Download Swinburne's privacy guidelines
March 2014
Privacy statementPrivacy Collection NoticeCybersecurity Hub
